

# NORALUK CHOTIBUTH

software developer

- +66944655757
- noraluk.kn@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/noraluk-chotibuth
- Suphanburi, Thailand 72130

# **EDUCATION**

O 2015 - 2019
Bachelor of Engineering
Technology

Thai-Nichi Institute of Technology

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Python
- MongoDB
- ProgreSQL
- NodeJS
- Golang
- Flutter
- Docker
- React Nextjs with Typescript

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Thai
- English

## **AWARDS**

**IELTS ACADEMIC - 23/09/2023** 

Overall Band Score: 6.5

Listening: 6.0Reading: 7.5Writing: 6.0Speaking: 5.5

## **ABOUT ME**

Software Developer with 4+ years experience in building and supporting features. I always get many opportunities for coding a new languages, which I have never coded it before and I can make it finish. I'm currently looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into a role as a Software Developer.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

O Dec 2018 - May 2020 Lightnet (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

# Backend Developer

- Developed web blockchain platform using Golang, NodeJS, and Solidity.
- Worked in Agile Scrum team environment.
- Used RESTful API and GRPC to connect each services.
- Managed efficient SQL queries and data transport.

Jun 2020 - Mar 2022 Siam Cement Group

# Fullstack Developer

- Using Python to collect data from customers and make a report per day.
- Coding UI of mobile application by Flutter.
- Mar 2022 Present

KASIKORN Business-Technology Group

#### Software Developer

- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Maintained former features and built a new one by coding Golang.
- Estimated work hours and tracked progress using Scrum methodology.
- Used NoSQL to manage data.
- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.